Guide to the Harper & Row, Publishers Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series X: Photographs
  - Thayer, Charles
  - Thelen, Herbert
  - Thomas, B. Brooks
  - Thomas, Evan
  - Thomas, Hugh (Box 340)
  - Thomas, Ruth
  - Thompson, Charles
  - Thompson, Joan Berengild
  - Thomson, Helen
  - Thomson, Jane
  - Thomson, Stewart
  - Thorbecke, Ellen
  - Thruelsen, Richard
  - Timmons, Bascom
  - Thurber, James P.
  - Tolbert, Frank
  - Toklas, Alice B.
  - Tolstoy, Alexandra
  - Tomkins, Calvin
  - Tomlinson, H. M.
  - Tompkins, Peter
  - Toulman and Goodfield
  - Travers, Hugh
  - Travers, P. L.
  - Treat, Lawrence
  - Trelease, Dr. Allen
  - Trescott, Paul B.
  - Trevor, Elleston
  - Trevor-Roper, H. R.
  - Trewhitt, Henry L.
  - Trivas, Irene
  - Trotsky, Leon
  - Tucker, Augusta
  - Tunley, Roul
  - Turner, Henry (Box 341)
  - Tyan, Kenneth
  - Underwood, Hgness
  - Uptown Pictures See: Gitlin, Todd
  - Updike, John P.
  - Urdang, Constance
  - Vaeth, J. Gordon
  - Vaillant, George A.
  - Valens, E. G.
  - Vandercook, John W.
  - Vandivert, Sam
  - Van Doren, Carl
  - Van Doren, Charles
  - Van Dersen, Glyndon G.
  - Vandiver, Frank Everson
  - Van Druten, John
  - Van Gulik, R. H.
  - Van Riper, Chas.
  - Van Slingerland, Peter
  - Varley, John M.
  - Vasiliu, Mircea
  - Vatsek, Joan
  - Velie, Lester
  - Vergara, Joe
  - Vergara, William C.
  - Vestal, Stanley
  - Vidich, Arthur
  - Vogel, Virgil H. J.
  - Von Dorsal, William R.
  - Wade, Mason
  - Wagner, Constance
  - Wagner, Friedelind
  - Wagner, Rudolph, Dr
  - Waldron, D'Lynn
  - Walker, D. E.
  - Walker, Stanley
  - Wall, Bernard
  - Wallace, Paul
  - Wallace, Sarah Leslie
  - Wallace Willard M.
  - Walsh, Chad
  - Walters, Anne
  - Warren, Carl
  - Warnke, Janice
  - Warren, Joyce
  - Ways, Max
  - Weber, Rubin
  - Watson, Virginia
  - Waxman, Julia
  - Weavers, The
  - Wecter, Dixon
  - Weig, Melvin
  - Weinberg, Martin
  - Weizmann, Chaim
  - Weizmann, Vera
  - Wellershoff, Dieter
  - Welles, Sam
  - Wells, George & Iris (Box 342)
  - Wells, Orson
  - Wells, Sumner
  - Werth, Alexander
  - Wescott, Glenway
  - Wessel, Mrs. Walter, W.
  - West, Paul
  - Westbrook, Perry D.
  - Westley, Bill & Leila Roosevelt
  - Weston, Christine
  - Weyer, Edward, Jr.
  - Whalley, Peyer
  - Wheeler, Elmer P.
  - Wheeler and Goldhor
  - White, Doris
  - White, Lynn
  - White, M. E.
  - White, Max
  - White, Reginald James
  - White, Robin
  - White, W. S.
  - Whiting, Frank M.
  - Whyte, Lancelot Law
  - Wicker, Tom
  - Wiener, Dr. Daniel N.
  - Wilchek, Stella
  - Wilcox, Francis O.
  - Wiley, Bell Irvin
  - Williams, Alan
  - Williams, Colin J.
  - Williams, Eric
  - Williams, Gluyas P.
  - Williams, Henry L. & Ottalie K.
  - Williams, Winnie
  - Willock, Ruth
  - Willaughley, Amea
  - Wilmot, Chester
  - Wilson, Allan N.
  - Wilson, Charles Morrow
  - Wilson, Ethel
  - Wilson, Sloan
  - Wilson, Woodrow (Box 343)
  - Winkler, Max
  - Winks, Robin W.
  - Winslow, Thyra Samter
  - Winston, Robert A, Lt.
  - Winnar, Frances
  - WIse, Arthur
  - Wish, Harvey
  - Wolf, John B.
  - Wolfe, Thomas
  - Wolfe, Winifred
  - Wolff, Leon
  - Wolheim, Donald
  - Wong, Jade Snow
  - Wood, Nancy
  - Woodfin, Henry
  - Woodham-Smith, Cecil
  - Woods, William Crawford
  - Woolf, Douglas
  - Woolrich, Corneil
  - Worth, Helen
  - Wright, Andrew
  - Wright, Gordon
  - Wright, Harold Bell
  - Wright, Louis B.
  - Wright, Richard
  - Wriston, Henry Merritt
  - Wyckoff, Jerome
  - Yarmon, Morton
  - Yarmolinsky, Adam
  - Yates, Raymond F.
  - Yates, Brock
  - Yila
  - Yorck, Ruth
  - Youd, Samuel
  - Young, Andrew
  - Young, Desmond
  - Young, Francis Brett
  - Young, Robert R.
  - Young, Thomas
  - Zaehringer, Alfred J.
  - Zaidenberg, Arthur
  - Zeimer, Patsy
  - Zern, Ed.
  - Ziff, William B.
  - Zimmerman, J. E.
  - Zinsser, Bill & Stevenson, James
  - Zuckerman, Solly Zweig, Paul
- Series XI: Photographs and Illustrations Negatives
  - Amory, Cleveland (Box 344)
  - Armstrong, Hamilton Fish
  - Astor, Brooke
  - Ata-ullah, Mohammed
  - Axthelm, Peter
  - Baldwin, Hanson
  - Ball, Harriet
  - Barley, Ann
  - Barlow, James
  - Bartlett, Sy
  - Batchelder, Marjorie
  - Bayles, William D.
  - Benchley, Robert
  - Berton, Roueshe
  - Bingham, Millicent Todd
  - Blake, Nicholas
  - Blanc, Suzanne
  - Boardman, Neil S.
  - Bowles, Chester
  - Boyce, Burke
  - Brenner, Anita
  - Brogan, D. W.
  - Bromfield, Louis
  - Brooks, Richard
  - Bryant, Arthur
  - Burns, James Macgregpr
  - Calaham, Harold Augustin
  - Canfield Sr., Cass
  - Canfield, Mrs. Cass
  - Canfield, Mary Cass
  - Carney, Aubrey
  - Carr, A. L.
  - Carrell, Alexisd
  - Carrington, Richard
  - Carson, Rachel
  - Chapin, Katharine Garrison
  - Chase, Jr., Francis
  - Chase, Stuart
  - Cleveland, Reginald
  - Cobean, Sam
  - Collins, Clella Reeves
  - Connolly, Cyril
  - Cook, Gladys Emerson
  - Cooper, III, John C. (John Cobb)
  - Cooper, Louise Field
  - Corbett, Sidney
  - Cores, Lucy
  - Cowles, Virginia
  - Coyle, Kathleen
  - Crisler, Lois
  - Crossman, H. Richard
  - Crow, Carl
  - Croy, Homer
  - Cullen, Countee
  - Cunti, Merle
  - Dart, Raymond A.
  - David, Evan
  - Davis, H. L.
  - Davis, Ruth
  - Davison, Edward
  - De Chant, John A.
  - De Ford, Sara
  - De Jong, David
  - Deland, Margaret
  - Dickens, Monica
  - Direen, Joseph
  - Dixon, H. Vernor
  - Donovan, Robert
  - Douglas, William (Box 345)
  - Drucker, Peter
  - Drury, Aubrey
  - Dryer, Bernard Victor
  - Dublen, Dr. Louis I.
  - Ducharmes, Jacques
  - Dufour, Charles L.
  - Dugan, James
  - Dulles, Foster Rhea
  - Duncan, Dorothy
  - Dunn, katherine
  - Dunphy, Jack
  - Dupuy, R. Ernest & Dupuy
  - Trevor N.
  - Eaton, Allen
  - Eaton, Evelyn
  - Eckstine, Gustav
  - Edwards, Phil
  - Ehrlich, Max
  - Embrie, Edwin R.
  - Engstrand, David
  - Ertz, Susan
  - Fair, Ronald L.
  - Faure, Raoul C.
  - Feinberg, Dr. Samuel
  - Feinburgh, Wilfred
  - Fermor, Patrick Leigh
  - Ferril, Thomas Hornsby
  - Filer, Tom
  - Filler, Louis
  - Fineberg, Salomon A.
  - Fineh, Edith
  - Finletter, Gretchen
  - Finn, Rev. William J.
  - Fischer, Louis
  - Fischer, Marooshka
  - Fisher, Roger
  - Fisher, Vardis
  - Flavin, Martin
  - Footner, Hulbert
  - Foster, Elizabeth
  - Fromm, Bella
  - Fuller, Blair
  - Fuller, Edmund
  - Fuller, Major J. F. C.
  - Funk, Charles Earle
  - Gascoigne, Bamber & Christina
  - Gaskin, Catherine
  - Gershoy, Leo
  - Gibb, George S.
  - Gies, Joseph
  - Gillies, Mary Davis
  - Gipson, Fred
  - Gleason, Edmund S.
  - Goldknopf, David
  - Gordon, Fred
  - Gould, Franklin F.
  - Gouldina, Phil
  - Grant, Leslie
  - Gray, George W.
  - Green, Anne
  - Green, Julian
  - Green, Martin
  - Green, Paul
  - Greenberg, David
  - Grendley, Janet Gillespie
  - Griffith, Thomas
  - Grisman, Arnold
  - Gruenberg, Sidonie Matsner
  - Hadas, Moses
  - Halacy, D. S., Jr.
  - Halper, Albert (Box 346)
  - Hansen, Thorkild
  - Hardy, Linsey
  - Hartman, Lee Foster
  - Haughland, Vern
  - Hawkins, Gerard
  - Heath, W. L.
  - Helmy, Mackinley
  - Herdman, Ramona
  - Hill, Russell
  - Hinton, Harold B.
  - Hoagland, Kathleen
  - Hoffer, Eric
  - Hoffmung, Gerard
  - Holton, Edith Austin
  - Hopkins, Stanley
  - Howard, Elizabeth Jane
  - Howe, Helen
  - Hubbell, Jay B.
  - Hughes, Ted
  - Hunt, George P.
  - Hunt, Morton
  - Huot, Louis C.
  - Hurd, Charles
  - Hurst, Fanny
  - Huxley, Aldous
  - Huxley, Julian
  - Jay, Charlotte
  - Johnson, Gerald
  - Johnson, Sally Patrick
  - Joseph, Richard
  - Kahn, Joan
  - Kahn, Roger
  - Kalashnikoff, Nicholas
  - Karpin, Fred L.
  - Kates, George N.
  - Kaye-Smith, Sheila
  - Keating, William J.
  - Kelland, Clarence
  - Kendall, Carol
  - Keyes, Frances Parkinson
  - King, Dr. Martin Luther
  - Kinmont, Jill
  - Kouwenhoven, John A.
  - Krasner, William
  - Krivitsky, W. G.
  - Krythe, Maymie
  - Kuroki, Ben
  - Lach, Alma
  - LaFollette, Suzanne
  - Laird, Jean
  - Lamb, Dana & Virginia
  - Lamont, Thomas (Box 347)
  - Langer, William L.
  - Lansdale, Edward Maj. Gen.
  - Lapp, Ralph
  - Laumer, Keith
  - Laver, James
  - Lee, Asher
  - Leggett, John
  - Leigh, James
  - Levitt, Saul
  - Lewinsohn, Richard
  - Lichtner, Marvin
  - Lilienthal, David E.
  - Lindap, Audrey
  - Lindey, Alexander
  - Lippman, Walter
  - Lloyd, A. E.
  - Lobell, Nathan D.
  - Lobsenz, Herbert
  - Lolos, Kimon
  - Lord, Walter
  - Loughlin, David
  - Loveridge, Arthur
  - Lowdermilk, Walter K.
  - Lukacs, John
  - Lundberg, Ferdinand
  - Luria, Jack
  - Lyon, Dana
  - McCabe, Charles R.
  - McCoy, John Pleasant
  - McCune, Wesley
  - McFee, William
  - McLead, A. S.
  - McMurry, George H.
  - McSorley, Edmond
  - McAdams, Lewis
  - MacGregor, Frank S.
  - Macmillan, Harold
  - Maddock, Allison
  - ManKiewicz, Dan
  - Marcham, F. G.
  - Markel, Lester
  - Martin, Ralph
  - Martle, Margaret
  - Manle, Frances
  - Maurois, Andre
  - Mazo, Earl
  - McCormick, Robert C.
  - McKenna, Richard
  - McKenney, Ruth
  - Mehta, Ved
  - Meyer, Edith
  - Millay, Edna St. Vincent
  - Miller, Nolan
  - Mitchell, Ronald
  - Molinaro, Ursule
  - Moley, Raymond
  - Moore, Msgr.
  - Morgenthan, Henry Jr.
  - Morris, I. V.
  - Morris, Marjorie, and Saners, Dan
  - Moris, William and Mary
  - Morris, Willie
  - Moyers, Bill
  - Murphy, Gardner
  - Murphy, Grace E. Barstow
  - Murray, Pauli
  - Mydans, Carl
  - Murdal, Gunnar
  - Neider, Charles
  - New Yorker Album, The (Box 348)
  - Newberry, Clare
  - Newman, William S.
  - Nock, Albert Jay
  - Noguchi, Isamn
  - Norris, Frank
  - Nuccio, Sal
  - Obarth, Herman
  - O'Brien, Kate
  - Ochs, Adolph
  - Ogburn, Charlton
  - Opdycke, John Baker
  - Osborne, Margaret
  - Pach, Walter
  - Palatin, Dr. Phillip
  - Palmer, Stuart
  - Parks, David
  - Peattie, Roderick
  - Peffer, Nathaniel
  - Pendray, G. Edward
  - Perventsev, Arkady A.
  - Pfeiffer, John
  - Picken, Mary Brooks
  - Pickrel, Paul
  - Piernal, Armund
  - Pinkerton, Robert E.
  - Plutzik, Hyam
  - Porter, Elias H.
  - Pratt, Fletcher
  - Priestley, Job
  - Procter, Maurice
  - Prokosch, Frederick
  - Pugh, Marshall
  - Radhakrishnan, Sarvepalli
  - Raisz, Erwin
  - Ran, Santha Rhama
  - Reston, James
  - Reves, Emery
  - Reynolds, Quentin
  - Rice, John
  - Rieff, Phillip
  - Ripley, Dillon
  - Robinson, Jane
  - Rodman, Selden
  - Roe, Ivan
  - Rogers, Samnuel
  - Rollins, Alise R.
  - Roosevelt, Kermit
  - Ross, Ishbel
  - Rubin, Michael
  - Rugh, Dr. Roberts
  - Sack, John
  - Sagan, Francoise
  - St. Hill, Thomas Nast
  - Samson, Erin
  - Saundby, Sir R.
  - Saxton, Eugene F.
  - Scanelli, Francis P.
  - Schoenbrun, Floyd
  - Schumpeter
  - Searls, Hank
  - Seifest, Mary Harris
  - Selle, Earl Albert
  - Settle, Mary Lee
  - Shaw, Harry
  - Shea, Nancy
  - Sheldon, William R.
  - Sherwood, Robert
  - Simonson, Lee
  - Slater, Jerome
  - Smith, G. Milton
  - Smith, Merriman (Box 349)
  - Smith, Philip Hillyer
  - Smith, Robert
  - Sokol, Erich
  - Sparks, Dorothy
  - Spring, Howard
  - Steele, Max
  - Stevens, Donald
  - Stimpson, George
  - Stimpson, Henry L.
  - Stowman, Knud
  - Straley, John A.
  - Streeter, Edward R.
  - Streit, Clarence
  - Sumner, G. Lynn
  - Swing, Raymond
  - Sykes, Christopher
  - Symes, Lilian
  - Symors, Julian
  - Tabrah, Ruth
  - Tautri, K'tut
  - Tate, Sylvia
  - Taylor, Deems
  - Taylor, Francis Henry
  - Taylor, Makwell D.
  - Tchelitchew, Pavel
  - Tevis, Walter
  - Thomas, Hugh
  - Thomas, Ruth
  - Thompson, Jim
  - Thorbeske, Ellen
  - Thurber, James
  - Travers, P. L.
  - Tomlinson, H. M.
  - Trelease, Dr. Allen
  - Tucher, Augusta
  - Tucker, Dr.
  - Underwood, Haness
  - Vandercook, John W.
  - Van Doren, Charles
  - Vasiliv, Mircea
  - Vatsek, Joan
  - Velie, Lester
  - Vergara, William C.
  - Wade, Mason
  - Wagner, Friedelind
  - Waldran, D'Lynn
  - Wallace, Paul
  - Ward, Robert
  - Weizmann, Chaim
  - Wells, Sumner
  - Werth, Alexander
  - Wescott, Glenway
  - Wessel, Mrs. Walter W.
  - West, Paul
  - Wheeler, Joseph L.
  - Wicker, Tom
  - Wiliams, Eric
  - Willoughby, Amea
  - Winwar, Frances
  - Wish, Harvey
  - Wolfe, Thomas
  - Wong, Jade Snow
  - Wright, Richard
  - Wriston, Henry Merrill
  - Wyckoff, Jerome
  - Yates, Raymond
  - Yates, Brock
  - Yila
  - Yorck, Ruth
  - Youna, Francis Brett
  - Zaehringer, Alfred J.
  - Ziff, William B.
  - Zuckerman, Sir Solly
  - Miscellaneous printed material (Box 350)